PayHook tests payment webhook idempotency locally.
Payment providers can send duplicate or retried webhook events.
Returning 200 OK does not always mean your internal state is correct.
This demo handler has a common bug: it processes the same checkout event twice.
PayHook sends a duplicate Stripe-style checkout.session.completed event.
The webhook returns 200 OK, but PayHook catches duplicate payment, fulfillment, and ledger state.
Now the demo handler switches to event-id deduplication.
PayHook runs the same duplicate webhook scenario again.
The fixed handler now ends in the correct state.
How do you test payment webhook idempotency today?